What is happening is we'll just go on the screenshot.
Uh, reset, see, the reset year was successful.
Hm.
So when, when we initially call that API during the first API
call for the reset, uh, what happens is, uh, the
course, uh, the, the course which we, uh, the school which, uh,
we deleted, uh, where the course was assigned, so that one doesn't
get added.
But when we do this, do it a second time, it is
added properly. So that is the
-- issue. One minute, one minute. So, so what is the functionality here?
What should be the functionality here? Say you you have assigned the
first you added the course to a school, then you
reassociated the school to the course to another school.
Both were created by the or added by the verifier. So
now you are uh deleting the second school.
So after deletion of the second school when you are not resetting,
so what will happen to the course? Where will it get associated
because the association is gone now for that course.
-- So what will happen? So the course in essentially gets deleted when
we delete the school.
But when we do a reset, the idea is or
-- the association gets deleted.
-- uh the course also gets deleted.
So with
this example, I mean, we can try with this one,
-- so I think.
Would it be like this, or is the, um, in a
database it is like this because the course isn't the course an
independent entity, uh, independent of the school because you
can reassociate to any school.
-- Yeah, but, uh,
hm, but, uh, where will that course uh be assigned then?
In the,
-- in the course list shouldn't it be there?
-- Uh, we can check that. Uh, we can try it. Uh, I'm,
uh, I also got confused now. Uh,
so, uh, your question is valid. I, I just, uh, got confused.
I, what is the ID? 5773.
Hm
2024. I'll select this one.
This is a test now.
And I
Currently, no schools are added by uh verified, right? So I'll add
one school.
And uh so you are allocated 100% to this project or you're
working on other project also?
-- No, I have um the, the allocation, but I don't know, but
uh I'm given some APT tasks from um AA for schools also.
Uh, I think 5656 tickets uh are there.
-- OK. So you are switching based on the tickets. Uh
-- yes.
-- OK.
So we have these courses, right? We'll select one of um course
name computer. We'll select this one.
Oh school, Academy of Computer Technology. OK.
Do a reassociation with Alaska Bible.
OK.
I see.
Now, I need to go ahead and delete.
Firstly, we'll check if that course was added to Alaska.
Yeah.
We have
Um, to go and delete Alaska Bible.
OK.
OK. What happened to that course?
See the course also got deleted.
There's no computer courses. Now,
what I do, what I'll do is I'll click on reset.
-- So yeah Um.
Yeah, only the associated courses are there, so how, so
-- they do soft delete.
Mm.
So now I'll uh call this reset functionality.
OK. If you see, there was no computer course added, right? In
the response also you'll see.
Is it there? I don't see it.
-- This is a school name.
-- Uh, this is a school name. That is fine. Uh, we don't
see that computer course here. So now I'll do a reset again.
See, the course gets added now.
So this is the issue. You can use this ID which
is mentioned in the
Uh,
take it and try to analyze why this is happening. You got
it right. So first time.
The course was not available, but 2nd time.
It is a
-- Can you please just uh reiterate the thing uh.
-- So, uh, uh, so you got the scenario, right? How, how to
reproduce this? Well, yeah, so about the reset button. So what reset
does is, so there's a separate table from where it just, uh,
takes, uh, whatever the initial data was and adds to our, uh,
uh, I mean the mod uh database. So that is what the
reset functionality does. But currently what is happening is when we click
on the reset.
And uh try to check like if the courses are
reset properly. So for the first click it is not happening, but
for the second time it is happening. The reset is working properly
for the second instance, not for the 1st. So that
-- is the we have to check the payload is going in the
first reset and the reset
-- is fine. See, in the payload we just have application here, nothing
much. Oh, OK. See, it's the
IED an application here. So, uh, basically, uh, just need
to confirm what uh is different, uh different in both the
request uh from. Uh
Uh, you can just check the locks.
So you'll find uh uh where exactly uh that particular lambda
is. I'm also not sure. So you can just go through the
code, try to check based on the uh API uh based on
this API coursework API, what exactly is going wrong.
And then you can just add a comment in the ticket uh
mentioning uh this can be the issue or uh if you
don't, don't find it, just text me like whatever your observation is.
-- OK.
-- Got it, right?
-- Mhm. Yeah.
-- OK then, uh, uh, before you log out, just, uh, uh, just
let me know. I mean, whatever.
-- Yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
-- OK, fine. Thanks.
-- Yeah, thank you. Bye.