What is happening is we will just go on the screenshot.
The reset was successful.
-- When we initially called the tape, during the first tape call for the reset, what happens is the course which we deleted where the course was assigned.
When we do this second time, it is added properly.
-- That is the issue.
-- What is the functionality here?
-- You have assigned the first you added the course to a school.
The course is essentially deleted when we delete the school.
-- When we do a reset, the idea is to get deleted.
This example we can try with this one.
-- We can check that.
I am also got confused.
-- The question is valid.
I think of five or six tickets.
-- You are switching based on the tickets.
Yes.
-- We have this course.
We will select one.
-- We will select one.