What is happening is we'll just go on the screenshot.
Uh, reset, see, the reset year was successful.
Hm.
So when, when we initially called the API during the first API call for the reset, uh, what happens is, uh, the course, uh, the, the course which we, uh, the school which, uh, we deleted, uh, where the course was assigned, so that one doesn't get added. But when we do this, uh, do it a second time, it is added properly. So that is the
issue. One minute, one minute. So, so what is the uh functionality here? What should be the functionality here? Say you you have assigned the first you added the course to a school, then you reassociated the school to the course to another school. Both were created by the or added by the verifier. So now you are uh deleting the second school. So after deletion of the second school when you are not resetting, so what will happen to the course? Where will it get associated because the association is gone now for that course.
So what will happen? So the course in essentially gets deleted when we delete the school. But when we do a reset, the idea is deleted
or the association gets deleted.
School uh the course also gets deleted.
So with this example, I mean, we can try with this one, so I think.
Would it be like this or is a um in a database, it is like this because the course isn't the course an independent entity, uh, independent of the school because you can reassociate to any school.
Yeah, but, uh, hm, but, uh, where will that course uh be assigned then? In
the, in the course list shouldn't it be there?
Uh, we can check that. Uh, we can try it. Uh, I'm, uh, I also got confused now. Uh, so, uh, your question is valid. I, I just, uh, got confused. I, what is the ID? 5773.
Hm
2024. I'll select this one.
This is a test now.
And I
Currently, no schools are added by uh verified, right? So I'll add one school.
And uh so you are allocated 100% to this project or you're working on other project also?
No, I have um the, the allocation, but I don't know, but uh I'm given some APT tasks from um Agus for schools also. Uh, I think 5656 tickets uh are there.
OK, so you are switching based on the tickets.
Yes.
OK.
So we have these courses, right? We'll select one of um course name computer. We'll select this one.
Oh school, Academy of Computer Technology. OK.
Do a reassociation with Alaska Bible.
OK.
I see.
Now, I need to go ahead and delete. Firstly, we'll check if that course was added to Alaska. Yeah. We have it.
Um, to go and delete Alaska Bible.
OK.
OK. What happened to that course?
See, the course uh also got deleted.
There's no computer courses. Now, what I do, what I'll do is I'll click on reset.
So yeah Um Yeah, only the associated courses are there. So how, so every
day they do soft delete.
Mm.
So now I'll uh call this reset functionality.
OK. If you see, there was no computer course added, right? In the response also you'll see.
Is it there? I don't see it.
This is the school name.
Uh, this is a school name. That is fine. Uh, we don't see that computer course here. So now I'll do a reset again.
See, the course gets added now. So this is the issue. You can use this ID which is mentioned in the Uh, take it and try to analyze why this is happening. You got it, right? So first time. The course was not available, but 2nd time. It is a
Can you please just uh reiterate the thing uh.
So, uh, uh, so you got the scenario, right? How, how to reproduce this? Well, so about the reset button. So what reset does is, so there's a separate table from where it just, uh, takes, uh, whatever the initial data was and adds to our, uh, uh, I mean the mod uh database. So that is what uh the reset functionality does. But currently what is happening is when we click on reset. And, uh, try to, uh, check like uh if the courses are reset properly. So in for the first click, it is not happening, but for the second time it is happening. The reset is working properly for the second instance, not for the 1st. So that
is the we have to check the payload is going in the first reset and the reset
is fine. See, in the payload we just have application here, nothing much. Oh, OK. See, there's the IED an application here. So, uh, basically, uh, just need to confirm what uh is different, uh different in both the request uh from. Uh Uh, you can just check the locks. So you'll find uh uh where exactly uh that particular lamb is. I'm also not sure. So you can just go through the code, try to check based on the uh API uh based on this API coursework API, what exactly is going wrong. And then you can just add a comment in the ticket uh mentioning uh this can be the issue or uh if you don't, don't find it, just text me like whatever your observation is.
OK.
Got it, right?
Mhm,
yeah.
OK then, uh, uh, before you log out, just, uh, uh, just let me know. I mean, whatever.
Yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
OK, fine. Thanks.
Oh yeah, thank you. Bye.